爸爸走了
Look, Dad's gone now.
我们得继承他的遗志
We have to carry out his legacy.
那就是
And that means hunting down.
能猎杀多少凶鬼恶灵杀多少
as many evil sons of bitches as we possibly can.
（忆往昔）
- 莉莎 - 迪恩
- Lisa. - Dean.
如果你想多留一阵
if you wanna stick around for a while…
你可以留下
you're welcome to stay.
我不能
I can't.
我还有很多工作
I got a lot of work to do.
这也不是我的生活
And it's not my life.
她真名叫贝拉·塔伯特
Bela Talbot's her real name.
我为特定客户获取一些独特的东西
I procure unique items for a select clientele.
贼
A thief.
是神偷
A great thief.
萨姆 你想打破迪恩的恶魔交易
Sam, you wanna break Dean free of that demon deal…
答案是不会写在哪本书里的
you ain't gonna find the answer in no book.
那要去哪找 鲍比
Then where, Bobby?
小子 我知道就好了
Kid, I wish I knew.
我一直在努力保住你的命 迪恩
I've been busting my ass trying to keep you alive, Dean.
你却一副毫不在乎的样子
And you act like you couldn't care less.
我不希望你担心我 迪恩
I don't want you to worry about me, Dean.
我要你担心你自己
I want you to worry about you.
我要你在乎你要死了这件事
I want you to give a crap that you're dying.
每个可恶的恶魔 都曾是人类吗
Every damn demon, they were all human once?
每个我见过的都是
Every one I've ever met.
对了 答案是「是」
The answer is yes, by the way.
你也会遭遇一样的事
Same thing will happen to you.
根本没办法让我不下地狱 是吧
There's no way of saving me from the pit, is there?
对
No.
（如今）
不好意思
I'm sorry.
先生
Sir?
醒醒
Wake up.
醒醒 听到了吗 醒醒
Wake up, you hear me? Wake up.
先生 醒醒
Sir, wake up!
救命
Help!
这里需要帮助
I need some help in here!
[邪恶力量 第3季第10集]
干杯
Cheers.
你在这里啊 你干什么呢
There you are. What are you doing?
喝酒
Having a drink.
这才下午2点 你还喝上威士忌了
It's 2 in the afternoon. You're drinking whiskey?
- 我一向喝威士忌 - 你才不
- I drink whiskey all the time. - No, you don't.
而且这有什么大不了
And what's the big deal?
你也会在酒吧买醉
You get sloppy in bars,
经常泡妞
you hit on chicks all the time.
我怎么就不行
Why can't I?
这里选择不多啊
It's kind of slim pickings around here.
你是怎么了
What's going on with you?
我尽力了 迪恩
I tried, Dean.
做什么
To do what?
救你
To save you.
可以给我来杯威士忌吗 双份 不加冰
Could I get a whiskey, double, neat.
- 我说真的 迪恩 - 不 你喝醉了
- I'm serious, Dean. - No, you're drunk.
你要去的地方
I mean, where you're going…
你要变成的样子
what you're gonna become.
我无法阻止
I can't stop it.
我开始觉得或许露比也无法阻止
I'm starting to think maybe even Ruby can't stop it.
但其实 没人能救你
But really, the thing is, no one can save you.
我不一直这么说吗
What I've been telling you.
不 我不是这意思
No, that's not what I mean.
我是说 没人能救你 因为你不想被救
I mean, no one can save you because you don't wanna be saved.
你怎么能这么不在乎你自己
I mean, how can you care so little about yourself?
你是有什么毛病
What's wrong with you?
喂
Hello?
对 我是斯奈德森先生
Yes, this is Mr. Sniderson.
什么
What?
在哪
Where?
诊断是什么
So, what's the diagnosis?
我们进行了一切能想到的检测
We've tested everything we can think to test.
他似乎非常健康
He seems perfectly healthy.
但却陷入了昏迷
Except that he's comatose.
斯奈德森先生 你是他的紧急联系人
Mr. Sniderson, you're his emergency contact.
有什么我们该了解的情况吗
Anything we should know?
什么疾病
Any illnesses?
不 他从不生病 他都不感冒
No, he never gets sick. I mean, he doesn't even catch cold.
医生 你能做点什么吗
Doctor, is there anything you can do?
我很抱歉 但我们都不知道病因是什么
Look, I'm sorry, but we don't know what's causing it…
所以我们也不知道怎么治疗
so we don't know how to treat it.
他就是
He just…
睡着了
went to sleep.
再没醒来
and didn't wake up.
鲍比怎么会在匹兹堡
So, what was Bobby doing in Pittsburgh?
除非他是来度很无聊的假
Well, unless he was taking an extremely lame vacation…
他肯定是来办案的 是吧
I mean, he must have been working a job, right?
按说应该能看到些
Well, you think there'd be some sort of.
迹象 什么的
sign or something, you know?
研究
Research,
新闻剪报
news clippings…
甚至是披萨盒或啤酒罐
Or a frigging pizza box or a beer can.
这个怎么样
How about this?
鲍比啊 总是注意掩盖行踪
Good old Bobby, always covering up his tracks.
你能看出点头绪来吗
You make heads or tails of any of this?
「非洲梦根」
"Silene capensis, "
我完全不知道这是什么
which, of course, means absolutely nothing to me.
看 讣告
Here, obit.
「沃特·格雷格博士
"Dr. Walter Gregg,
64岁 大学神经学家「
64, university neurologist."
他怎么死的
How'd he bite it?
其实 死因不明
Actually, they don't know.
上面说 他睡着了 再就没醒来
They say he just went to sleep and didn't wake up.
听上去耳熟吗
That sound familiar to you?
好吧
All right…
或许鲍比在查博士的死亡
So let's say Bobby was looking into the doc's death.
在猎杀什么
You know, hunting after something…
那东西反开始猎杀他
That started hunting him.
对
Yeah.
好 你留下 看看能不能理出点头绪来
All right. Stay here. See if you can make heads or tails of this.
你打算干什么
What are you gonna do?
我自己去查查这位博士
I'm gonna look into the good doctor myself.
（西摩兰医学院 沃特·格雷格博士）
你是格雷格博士的实验室助理
So you're Dr. Gregg's lab assistant?
对
That's right.
他的死肯定让你很震惊
Well, his death must have come as a shock to you.
是的
Yeah, it did.
但是 在睡梦中安然离去
But, still, go in your sleep, peaceful…
你也会希望能如此吧
That's what you wish for, right?
是啊
Yeah. Right.
格雷格博士是研究睡眠障碍的吗
Dr. Gregg, uh, studied sleeping disorders?
梦
Dreams?
我不懂
I don't understand.
这一切我都跟另一位警探说过了
I went over all of this with the other detective.
已经有别的警探找过你了吗
You already spoke to another detective?
是的 一位和气的长胡子的老先生
Yes. A very nice older man with a beard.
如果可以 我想再听一遍
Well, I'd love to hear it again if you don't mind.
但是 我还挺忙 或许稍后的吧
Thing is, I'm sort of busy. Maybe we could do this later?
好啊 行
Sure. Yeah.
今天下午晚些时候我带你去趟警局
Just bring you down to the station later this afternoon.
把你的口供录下来 正式点
And get your statement on tape, do it all official-like.
好吧 我原本不知道格雷格博士做的实验
Look, okay, I didn't know about Dr. Gregg's experiments.
是我整理他文件时才发现的
Not until I was cleaning out his files.
他的实验是…
His experiments…?
关于睡眠的那些吗
The ones he was conducting on sleeping?
没人知道 大学不知道 谁都不知道
No one knew, okay? Not the university, not anybody.
我已经问过律师了
I already spoke with a lawyer,
他说 我不需要为任何事负责
and he told me that I can't be held liable for anything.
或许吧
Maybe you couldn't,
但那是新证据出现之前了
but that was before the new evidence came to light.
新证据
New evidence?
什么新证据
What new evidence?
这我不便透露
I'm not at liberty to say.
我只是个研究生 做这个只是为挣学费
Look, I'm just a grad student, this was a gig to cover tuition.
或许吧 但是…
Maybe so. But, uh, still this…
这可能会被记入你的永久记录
this could go on your permanent record.
除非你把博士的研究交给我
Unless you hand over the doctor's research to me.
全部给我
All of it.
（匹兹堡市警局）
我不知道宿舍助理说了什么
Look, I don't know what the RA said, but,
但我只是在种蕨类植物
I was growing ferns.
别激动 小子 我不是为此而来
Take it easy, Phish, that's not why I'm here.
是吗
Really?
谢天谢地 好吧
Thank God. Okay.
我想找你问问格雷格博士的睡眠研究
I wanna talk to you about Dr. Gregg's sleep study.
嗯 格雷格博士死了 是吧
Yeah. Dr. Gregg just died, right?
- 你曾是他的实验对象之一 是吧 - 嗯
- You were one of his test subjects, right? - Yeah.
除非你在执勤什么的
Unless you're on duty or whatever?
我也可以破个例
I guess I can make an exception.
格雷格博士在测试的治疗是针对
Now, Dr. Gregg was testing treatments for a,
「夏-威二氏综合征」的
"Charcot-Wilbrand syndrome"?
意思是
Which means…?
我
I…
我不能做梦
I can't dream.
我小时候出过自行车事故
I had this bike accident when I was a kid…
脑袋撞坏了
and I banged my head pretty good and.
此后再就没做过梦
I haven't had a dream since.
直到参与这项研究
Till the study. You know.
算是做了梦吧
Sort of.
博士给了你什么
What'd the doc give you?
一种黄色的茶
It's this yellow tea.
气味很恶心
It smelled awful,
尝起来更糟
tasted worse.
它有什么效果
What did it do?
我昏睡了过去
Just passed right out.
我做了个特别逼真强烈的梦
And I had the most vivid, super-intense dream.
- 就像不好的迷幻剂体验 - 了解
- Like a bad acid trip, you know? - Totally.
我…不了解
I mean, no.
就是这样
That was it.
之后我就退出了研究
I dropped out of the study right after that.
我不喜欢那感觉
I didn't like it.
老实说
To tell you the truth…
那让我害怕了
it kind of scared me.
他怎么样了
How is he?
没变化
No change.
你查到什么了
What you got?
根据你告诉我的博士的实验的事
Well, considering what you told me about the doc's experiments…
鲍比墙上的东西就能理出头绪来了
Bobby's wall is starting to make hell of a lot more sense.
- 怎么说 - 这种植物
- How so? - This plant, Silene capensis…
被称为非洲梦根
is also known as African Dream Root.
数世纪以来都有萨满巫师和巫医使用它
It's been used by shaman and medicine men for centuries.
我猜猜 他们服药
Let me guess. They dose up…
然后拿出土著乐器 跳起土著舞蹈
bust out didjeridus, and start kicking around the hackey.
不是的
Not quite.
如果你相信传说
If you believe the legends…
它是用于梦行的
it's used for dreamwalking.
进入他人的梦境
I mean, entering another person's dreams,
在他们脑袋里转悠
poking around in their heads.
那我们相信传说咯
I take it we believe the legends?
我们什么时候不信了
When don't we?
但梦行还只是冰山一角
But dreamwalking is just the tip of the iceberg.
什么意思
What do you mean?
这梦根法力强大
I mean, this Dream Root is some serious mojo.
如果你服得够多 练得够多
You take enough of it, with practice,
你基本上能成为《猛鬼街》里的弗莱迪
you can become a regular Freddy Krueger.
你可以控制一切
You can control anything.
你可以把噩梦变好
You could turn bad dreams good,
把好梦变坏
you could turn good dreams bad.
还能在人的梦里杀了他们
And killing people in their sleep?
可以
For example.
那么
So let's say…
假设博士拿他的病人试了这玩意
let's say this doc was testing this stuff on his patients,
就像当初测试迷幻剂的蒂姆·莱利
Tim Leary-style.
有人生他的气 便决定潜入他的梦境
Somebody gets pissed at him, decides to give him a dream visit…
他就长眠了
he goes nighty-night.
那鲍比呢
What about Bobby?
如果杀手也找上了他 他怎么还活着
I mean, if the killer came after him, how come he's still alive?
我不知道
I don't know.
救我
Help me!
谁救救我
Somebody help me!
救我
Help me!
我们要怎么找到杀人睡魔
So how do we find our homicidal sandman?
- 可能是任何人 - 是吗
- Could be anyone. - Yeah?
- 嗯 - 任何认识博士的人
- Yeah. - Anyone who knew the doctor.
还能拿到他的梦根
and had access to his dream shrooms.
或许是他的哪个实验对象
Maybe one of his test subjects or something?
可能吧 但他的研究不怎么靠谱
Possible. But his research was pretty sketchy. I mean…
我都不知道他有多少实验对象 他们是谁
I don't know how many subjects he had or who all of them were.
怎么了
What?
换了是其他案子 我们现在肯定会
In any other case, we'd be calling Bobby.
联系鲍比 向他求助
and asking him for help right now.
知道吗 你是对的
You know what? You're right.
什么
What?
我们去跟他谈吧
Let's go talk to him.
好啊 但那样对话可能会比较单边
Sure, I think we might find the conversation a bit one-sided.
除非我们也服用梦根
Not if we're tripping on some Dream Root.
- 什么 - 没错
- What? - You heard me.
你要去鲍比脑袋里梦行吗
You wanna go dreamwalking inside Bobby's head?
有何不可 或许我们能帮忙
Yeah. Why not? Maybe we could help.
我们都不知道里面有什么
We have no idea what's crawling around in there.
- 能有多糟 - 很糟
- How bad could it be? - Bad.
哥们 这可是鲍比
Dude, it's Bobby.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
但有个问题 我们没有非洲梦根
One problem, though, we're fresh out of African Dream Root.
除非你认识个能找到梦根的人
So unless you know someone who can score some…
- 该死 - 怎么了
- Crap. - What?
- 贝拉 - 贝拉
- Bela. - Bela?
该死
Crap.
你真是在提议我们向她求助吗
You're actually suggesting we ask her a favor?
我光想想都觉得恶心 但是的
I'm feeling dirty just thinking about it, but yeah.
萨姆
Sam.
贝拉 我没想到你真会来
Bela, I didn't think there's a chance in hell you'd show up.
我就是充满惊喜
Well, I'm full of surprises.
但说实话
Though, truthfully…
你想知道我为什么来吗
you wanna know why I'm here?
好
Okay.
因为你
Because of you.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
- 我脑子里都是你 - 什么
- I can't stop thinking about you. - What?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
萨姆 萨姆 萨姆
Sam. Sam. Sam.
萨姆 醒醒
Sam, wake up!
哥们 你睡得好香
Dude, you were out.
还发出了特幸福的叫声
And making some serious happy noises.
你梦到谁了
Who were you dreaming about?
什么 没谁 没有
What? No one. Nothing.
得了 告诉我吧
Come on. You can tell me.
- 安吉丽娜·朱莉 - 不是
- Angelina Jolie? - No.
- 布拉德·皮特吗 - 不是
- Brad Pitt? - No. No.
哥们 那不重要
Dude, it doesn't matter.
随便了
Whatever.
随便吧
我联系贝拉了
I called Bela.
贝拉 是吗
Bela? Yeah?
她怎么说的
What'd she, you know, say?
她会帮我们吗
She gonna help us?
令人震惊啊 不会 我们又回到了原点
Shockingly, no, which puts us back to square one.
我一直在破译博士的笔记
I've been trying to decipher the doctor's notes.
很遗憾 他的笔迹比你还潦草
Unfortunately, he has worse handwriting than you do.
你要来帮帮我吗
You wanna come help me with this stuff?
嗯 稍等下的
Yeah, yeah. Just give me a sec.
贝拉 真是没想到
Bela. As I live and breathe.
是你联系了我 记得吗
You called me. Remember?
我记得你拒绝了我
I remember you turning me down.
我就是充满惊喜
Well, I'm just full of surprises.
贝拉 你好吗
Bela. What's going on?
我给你拿来了非洲梦根
I brought you your African Dream Root.
很厉害的东西 不好得到
Nasty stuff, and not easy to come by.
怎么突然改变了心意
Why the sudden change of heart?
我就不能偶尔卖个人情了吗
What, I can't do you a little favor every now and again?
不 你不能
No. You can't.
说吧 我想知道你有什么条件
Now, come on, I wanna know what the strings are.
别事后再说
before you attach them.
你说这是为了鲍比·辛格 是吧
You said this was for Bobby Singer, right?
我是为了他 不是你
Well. I'm doing it for him, not you.
鲍比 为什么
Bobby? Why?
他救过我
He saved my life once.
在弗拉格斯塔夫
In Flagstaff.
我搞砸了 他救了我 好吗 满意了吗
I screwed up and he saved me, okay? You satisfied?
或许吧
Maybe.
我们什么时候一起踏上这趟魔法神秘之旅
So when do we go on this little magical mystery tour?
你哪都不去
You're not going anywhere.
我都不放心让你上我的车
I don't trust you enough to let you in my car,
更别提进入鲍比的脑袋了
much less Bobby's head.
别介意
No offense.
不介意
None taken.
现在是凌晨2点 我去哪啊
It's 2 a.m. Where am I supposed to go?
去开间房嘛
Get a room.
他们有魔法手指
They got the Magic Fingers,
还有付费色情片 你准喜欢
Casa Erotica on pay-per-view. You'll love it.
你…
You…
很高兴…见到你
Nice to… Seeing you…
贝拉
Bela.
我们要把灯光调暗
Well, should we dim the lights and.
听着《月之暗面》 看《绿野仙踪》吗
synch up Wizard of Oz to Dark Side of the Moon?
为什么啊
Why?
你上大学时都干什么了
What did you do during college?
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
可不能落了这个
Can't forget this.
给
Here.
这是什么
What the hell is that?
鲍比的头发
Bobby's hair.
我们得喝下鲍比的头发吗
We have to drink Bobby's hair?
这是控制你进入谁的梦境的方式
That's how you control whose dream you're entering.
你得喝下他们的
You got to drink some of their…
身体部分
Some of their body.
头发大概总比
Well, guess the hair of the dog.
其他身体部分强
is better than other parts of the body.
干杯
Bottoms up.
嗯
Yeah.
有感觉吗
Feel anything?
没有
No.
你有感觉吗
You feel anything?
没有
No.
或许是东西不好
Maybe we got some bad shwag.
什么时候开始下雨的
When did it start raining?
什么时候开始下逆向雨的
When did it start raining upside down?
好吧 我不知道哪个更怪
Okay, I don't know what's weirder,
我们在鲍比脑子里
the fact that we're in Bobby's head…
还是他梦到了《美好家园》杂志
or that he's dreaming of Better Homes and Gardens.
等等
Wait. Wait a sec.
想象这里没有上漆
Imagine the place without the paint job.
更凌乱 灰蒙蒙的 到处是书
More cluttered, dusty, books all over the place.
- 这是鲍比家 - 对
- It's Bobby's house. - Yeah.
鲍比
Bobby?
迪恩
Dean?
我要去外面看看
I'm gonna go look outside.
不 别分开
No, no, stay close.
哥们 我没事的 我就到处看看
Dude, I'll be fine. Just look around in here.
我们得找到他
Look, we gotta find him.
别干傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
迪恩
Dean!
鲍比
Bobby?
Bobby.
谁在外面
Who's out there?
鲍比 你在里面吗
Bobby, you in there?
- 迪恩 - 嗯 是我 开门
- Dean? - Yeah. It's me. Open up.
你怎么找到我的
How in the hell did you find me?
萨姆和我拿到了那什么梦根
Sam and I got our hands on some of that Dream Root stuff.
梦根 什么玩意
Dream Root? What?
格雷格博士 他的实验
Dr. Gregg, the experiments?
你说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
快
Hurry.
- 怎么回事 - 她来了
- What's going on? - She's coming.
好吧 你知道这是梦境吧
Okay, you know this is a dream, don't you?
你疯了吗
What are you, crazy?
这是梦 鲍比 这都不是真的
It's a dream, Bobby, none of this is real.
你看那像假的吗
Does that look made-up?
鲍比 那是谁
Bobby, who is that?
她…
She's…
她是我妻子
She's my wife.
为什么 鲍比
Why, Bobby?
你为什么要这么对我
Why did you do this to me?
我宁可死也不想伤害你
I would rather die myself than hurt you.
但你是伤害了我
But you did hurt me.
你拿刀捅了我
You shoved that knife into me.
一遍又一遍
Again and again.
你看着我流血
You watched me bleed.
看着我死去
Watched me die.
鲍比
Bobby,
- 她不是真的 - 你怎么能
- she's not real. - How could you?
你被附身了 宝贝
You were possessed, baby.
你当时都发狂了
You were rabid.
而我当时不知道我现在知道的东西
And I didn't know what I know now.
- 我不知道要怎么救你 - 你撒谎
- I didn't know how to save you. - You're lying.
你就想要我死
You wanted me dead.
如果你爱我 你总会找到办法的
If you'd loved me, you would've found a way.
- 对不起 - 快来
- I'm sorry. - Come on.
- 你是谁 - 你是谁
- Who are you? - Who are you?
你不属于这里
You don't belong here.
你也好意思说
You're one to talk.
你在我朋友脑袋里呢
You're in my friend's head.
那你真不会选朋友
Well, you got a poor choice in friends.
这是自卫 是他来找我麻烦的
This is self-defense. He came after me.
他想伤害我
He wanted to hurt me.
或许是因为你杀人了
Maybe because you're a killer.
你该对我更好些
You should be nicer to me.
你在这里
In here…
只是个虫子 我是神
you're just an insect. I'm a god.
相信我 这一切
I'm telling you, all of it.
这房子 你妻子 都是噩梦
Your house, your wife, it's a nightmare.
- 我杀了她 - 鲍比
- I killed her. - Bobby!
这是你的梦 你可以醒过来
This is your dream that you can wake up.
你可以做任何事
I mean, hell, you can do anything.
放过我吧 让她杀了我吧
Just leave me alone. Let her kill me already.
看着我
Look at me. Look at me.
你得马上醒过来
You gonna snap out of this now.
You gotta snap out of this now.
你不能死 我不能看着你死
You're not gonna die. I'm not gonna let you die.
我不能看着你死
I'm not gonna let you die.
你对我就像个父亲
You're like a father to me.
你得相信我 求你
You gotta believe me, please.
- 我在做梦吗 - 是的
- I'm dreaming? - Yes.
控制你的梦吧
Now take control of it.
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
相信吧
Believe it.
你可不可以醒过来
Now would you please wake up?
好梦
Sweet dreams.
鲍比
Bobby.
那…
That…
你妻子的那事
That stuff with… all that stuff with your wife?
那是真的吗
That actually happen?
每个人都有开始猎魔的原因
Everybody got into hunting somehow.
- 很遗憾 - 不必
- I'm sorry. - Don't be sorry.
要不是你 我还迷失在那里呢
If it weren't for you, I'd still be lost in there.
或是死了
Or dead.
谢谢
Thank you.
那个瘾君子没在宿舍里
So, uh, stoner boy wasn't in his dorm.
我猜他早跑了
My guess is that he's long gone by now.
- 他可不是瘾君子 - 是吗
- He ain't much of a stoner. - No?
嗯
No.
他叫杰里米·弗罗斯特
His name's Jeremy Frost.
是个天才 智商160呢
Full-on genius. Hundred-and-sixty IQ.
这很不得了
Which is saying something,
因为他爸爸曾拿棒球棒打过他的脑袋
considering his dad took a baseball bat to his head.
这位就是他的年度好爹
Here's Father of the Year.
他在杰里米10岁前就死了
He died before Jeremy was 10.
看上去真像个好人
Looks like a real sweetheart.
那伤导致他患上了夏-威二氏综合征
Injury gave him Charcot-Wilbrand,
他此后再没做过梦
he hasn't dreamt since.
直到他服下了梦药
Till he started dosing the dream drug.
对
Yep.
他怎么知道如何挖出你最可怕的噩梦
How'd he know how to dig up your worst nightmare.
拿来对付你
and throw it at you?
他在我脑袋里翻来翻去
He was rooting around in my skull.
天知道他在那里看到了什么
God knows what he saw in there.
他最初是怎么进去的
You know, how'd he get in there in the first place?
他不是需要有你的头发
Isn't he supposed to have your some of your hair,
或DNA吗
your DNA or something?
- 是啊 - 嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我知道是他前 他递给过我啤酒
Before I knew it was him, he offered me a beer.
我喝了
I drank it.
真是蠢极了
Dumbest frigging thing.
我不知道 也没那么蠢吧
I don't know. It wasn't that dumb.
迪恩 你不是吧
Dean, you didn't.
- 我当时渴了 - 好啊
- I was thirsty. - That's great,
这下他能找上你们俩任何一个了
now he can come after either one of you.
那我们就得先找到他了
Well, now, we'll just have to find him first.
我们最好快点找
We better work fast.
还要多喝咖啡
and coffee up.
因为我们绝不能睡着
Because one thing we cannot do is fall asleep.
（两天后）
这个杰里米又不是鬼魂
I mean, this Jeremy guy's not a frigging ghost.
他能去哪啊
Where the hell could he be?
迪恩 你真不需要我来开车吗
Dean, you sure you don't want me to drive?
你似乎有点…
You seem a little…
- 咖啡喝多了 - 多谢你告知了 天才
- caffeinated. - Well, thanks for the news flash, Edison.
拜托
Come on.
告诉我你有发现
Tell me you got something.
脱衣舞俱乐部没收获吗
Strip club was a bust?
嗯
Yeah.
那是最后的线索了
That was our last lead.
搞什么 鲍比
What the hell, Bobby.
别吼我 小子 我也忙得团团转呢
Don't yell at me, boy. I'm working my ass off here.
抱歉 我就是…累了
Sorry, I'm sorry. I'm just… I'm tired.
- 谁不呢 - 贝拉有线索吗
- Well, who ain't? - What's Bela got?
- 你查到什么了吗 贝拉 - 抱歉
- What do you got, Bela? - Sorry.
有时鬼魂们喜欢聊天
Sometimes the spirit world is in a chatty mood,
有时不喜欢
and sometimes it isn't.
- 她没发现 - 好啊
- She's got nothing. - Great.
那我要去崩了自己的脑袋了
Well, I'm just gonna go blow my brains out now.
我问你
Let me ask you something.
你为什么要帮我们
What are you doing helping us?
鲍比 你居然不记得了吗
Bobby, I'm surprised you don't remember.
弗拉格斯塔夫
Flagstaff?
哦
Yeah.
对
Right.
弗拉格斯塔夫
Flagstaff.
好吧 行了 我受够了
All right, that's it. I'm done.
你干什么
What are you doing?
睡个早该睡的觉
Taking myself a long-overdue nap.
什么
What?
迪恩 杰里米可能会来找你
Dean, Jeremy can come after you.
- 就要这样 - 什么
- That's the idea. - Excuse me?
拜托 我们既然找不到他 就让他来抓我吧
Come on, man, we can't find him, so let him come to me.
在他的地盘上吗 在他是个神的地方吗
On his own turf? Where he's basically a god?
我能应付得来
I can handle it.
你一个人不行
Not alone, you can't.
你干什么
What are you doing?
我跟你一起去
Coming in with you.
- 不行 - 为什么不行
- No, you're not. - Why not?
至少那样是两对一
At least then it'll be two against one.
因为我不希望你在我脑袋里转
Cause I don't want you digging around in my head.
那没办法
Too bad.
迪恩
Dean.
天啊
Jeez.
我的老天爷
For the love of God.
我们怎么还在这里
What are we still doing here?
我不知道
I have no idea.
外面有人
There's someone out there.
你要坐下吗
You gonna sit down?
来啊
Come on.
我们只有一小时
We only have an hour.
然后就得接棒球练习结束的本了
before we have to pick Ben up from baseball.
我从未做过这样的梦
I've never had this dream before.
别那么看我
Stop looking at me like that.
- 抱歉 - 迪恩
- Sorry. - Dean.
我爱你
I love you.
她去哪了
Where'd she go?
迪恩
Dean.
好吧
Okay.
迪恩
Dean?
杰里米
Jeremy?
迪恩
Dean.
你真是个帅小伙儿
Well, aren't you a handsome son of a gun.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
我懂了
I get it. I get it.
我是自己最可怕的噩梦吗
I'm my own worst nightmare, that it?
就像《超人3》里废品场的那段戏
Kind of like the Superman lll junkyard scene?
跟自己对打吗
A little mano y mano with myself?
随你怎么开玩笑 机灵鬼
Joke all you want, smart-ass.
但你无法对我撒谎 我知道真相
But you can't lie to me. I know the truth.
我知道你内心多枯萎
I know how dead you are inside.
你觉得自己多没用
How worthless you feel.
我知道你看着镜子时
I know how you look into a mirror…
恨自己的倒影
and hate what you see.
抱歉 伙计 那没用的
Sorry, pal, it's not gonna work.
你不是真的
You're not real.
我当然是真的
Sure I am.
- 我是你 - 我看不是
- I'm you. - I don't think so.
这是我的睡梦
See, this is my siesta.
不是你的
Not yours.
我只需要弹个指响 你就消失了
All I gotta do is snap my fingers and you go bye-bye.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你也别想跑
Neither are you.
就像我说的
Like I said…
我们得谈谈
we need to talk.
迪恩
Dean.
醒醒
Wake up.
天啊 你就是不知道见好就收 是吧
Boy, you just don't know when to leave well enough alone, do you?
你个疯子
You're a psycho.
你错了
You're wrong.
是吗 跟格雷格博士说啊
Yeah? Tell that to Dr. Gregg.
博士吗
The doc?
不 就是博士让我对这上瘾的
No, no. The doc's the one that got me hooked on this stuff.
然后又不让我用了
and then he took it away.
但我需要它 而他不肯给我
But I needed it, and he wouldn't let me have it.
所以你就杀了他
So you killed him?
我又能做梦了
I can dream again.
你知道那滋味吗 不能做梦
You know what that's like, not to be able to dream?
你永远得不到真正的休息
You never rest, not really.
感觉就像醒了15年
It's like being awake for 15 years.
我猜猜 那把你逼疯了吗
And let me guess, that makes you go crazy?
我只想被放过
I just wanna be left alone.
我只想做梦
I just wanna dream.
抱歉 不行
Sorry. Can't do that.
错误答案
That's the wrong answer.
我越来越擅长这个了
I'm getting better and better at this.
越来越强大了
Stronger and stronger all the time.
但你和你哥哥
But you and your brother…
你们醒不来了
you're not waking up.
这次不行了
Not this time.
我不会让你们醒来
I'm not gonna let you.
你要下地狱了
I mean, you're going to hell.
你都不肯想办法阻止吗
and you won't lift a finger to stop it?
什么叫低自尊啊
Talk about low self-esteem.
不过 你这条贱命大概也不值得拯救
Then again, I guess it's not much of a life worth saving.
醒醒 迪恩 快醒来
Wake up, Dean. Come on. Wake up.
毕竟 除了萨姆 你什么都没有
I mean, after all, you've got nothing, outside of Sam.
你什么都不是
You are nothing.
你就像只攻击犬一样无脑顺从
You're as mindless and obedient as an attack dog.
- 才不是呢 - 是吗
- That's not true. - No?
你想要什么
What are the things that you want?
你梦想什么
What are the things that you dream?
你的车 是爸爸的
I mean, your car, that's Dad's.
你最喜欢的皮夹克 爸爸的
Your favorite leather jacket, Dad's.
你喜欢的音乐 是爸爸喜欢的
Your music, Dad's.
你有自己的想法吗
Do you even have an original thought?
没有
No.
你就只有「照顾好萨姆
No, all there is is, "Watch out for Sammy.
照顾好你弟弟 小子「
Look after your little brother, boy!"
你脑袋里还能听到爸爸的声音 是吧
You can still hear your Dad's voice in your head, can't you?
- 清晰响亮 - 闭嘴吧
- Clear as a bell. - Just shut up.
想想看
When you think about it…
他一直在训练你
all he ever did was train you,
使唤你
boss you around.
但萨姆
But Sam…
萨姆 他很宠爱
Sam, he doted on.
- 他爱萨姆 - 我说真的
- Sam, he loved. - I mean it.
我越来越生气了
I'm getting angry.
爸爸知道你究竟是什么样的人
Dad knew who you really were.
一个好士兵而已
A good soldier and nothing else.
爸爸的小钝器
Daddy's blunt little instrument.
你亲生老爹都不在乎你的死活
Your own father didn't care whether you lived or died.
- 你为什么要在乎呢 - 混蛋
- Why should you? - Son of a bitch!
我父亲是个执迷的混蛋
My father was an obsessed bastard!
他丢给我的一切 让我保护萨姆
All that crap he dumped on me, about protecting Sam,
那是他的心结
that was his crap.
是他无力保护家人
He's the one who couldn't protect his family.
是他眼看着妈妈死去
He's the one who let Mom die.
是他没有照顾萨姆 我一直都在
Who wasn't there for Sam. I always was.
他不公平
He wasn't fair!
我不该因他承受这样的重担
I didn't deserve what he put on me.
我也不该下地狱
And I don't deserve to go to hell!
你别想逃过我 迪恩
You can't escape me, Dean.
你死定了
You're gonna die.
这 就是你将变成的模样
And this, this is what you're gonna become.
你无法阻止我
You can't stop me.
我在这里无所不能
There's nothing I can't do in here.
因为梦根
Because of the Dream Root.
对
That's right.
是吗
Yeah?
你忘了件事
Well, you're forgetting something.
什么事
What's that?
我也服了梦根
I took the Dream Root too.
杰里米
Jeremy!
不
No.
- 爸爸 - 我跟你说话时 你要回答 小子
- Dad? - You answer me when I'm talking to you, boy.
不
No.
你也在那里编织梦境了
So you did a little dream-weaving of your own in there?
嗯 我就集中了精神 然后就成了
Yeah. I just sort of concentrated and it happened, you know?
会不会是因为
Didn't have anything to do with…
你的灵力
you know, your psychic stuff?
不是
No.
应该不是吧
I mean, I don't think so.
很好
Good. Good.
你们见到贝拉了吗
You guys seen Bela?
她没在房间 也不接电话
She's not in her room, she's not answering her phone.
她肯定是走了
She must've taken off or something.
就那么走掉吗 奇怪啊
Just like that? It's a little weird.
是啊 要我说 奇怪的是
Yeah. Well, if you ask me, what's weird.
她为什么会答应帮我们
is why she helped us in the first place.
不是说你救了她一命吗
I thought you saved her life.
你说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
弗拉格斯塔夫那事
That thing in Flagstaff?
弗拉格斯塔夫有个护身符
That thing in Flagstaff was an amulet.
我跟她做了笔好交易而已
I gave her a good deal, that's all.
那她为什么…
Well, then why did…?
你们最好摸摸兜
You boys better check your pockets.
不是真让你们摸兜
Not literally.
不不
No, no, no.
柯尔特枪
The Colt.
贝拉偷了柯尔特枪
Bela stole the Colt.
该死 小子们
Damn it, boys.
收拾东西
Pack your crap.
干吗 我们去哪
Why? Where we going?
我们要去找到那贱人
We're gonna go hunt the bitch down.
萨姆 我想问
Sam, I was wondering.
你在我脑袋里时 都看到了什么
When you were in my head, what did you see?
就是杰里米 他把你我分开了
Just Jeremy. He kept me separated from you.
大概那样打扁我的脑袋更轻松吧
Easier to beat my brains out that way, I guess.
你呢 你没提起过
What about you? You never said.
没什么 我一直找你来着
Nothing. I was looking for you the whole time.
萨姆
Sam.
嗯
Yeah?
我想了很多
I've been doing some thinking.
我…
And…
是这样的
Well, the thing is…
我不想死
I don't wanna die.
我不想下地狱
I don't wanna go to hell.
那好吧
All right. Yeah.
我们会想办法救你的
We'll find a way to save you.
那好
Okay, good.
你别想逃过我 迪恩 你死定了
You can't escape me, Dean. You're gonna die.
这
And this?
就是你将变成的模样
This is what you're gonna become.